翻译　职业补坑的皮带断了
孩子们 我改主意了 我要继续主持大局 担任总裁 公司的一把手
Kids, I changed my mind. I'm staying on. As CEO. Head of the firm.
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
ZIMUXIA.CN
校对　职业补坑的皮带断了　时间轴　阿布
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
你阴了我一道
You fucked me.
压制　Jason肖
三年前 你还在精神病院
Three years ago, you were still in the nut house.
监制　职业补坑的皮带断了
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
爸 那叫疗养 而且我已经痊愈了
Dad, it's called rehab. And I'm in recovery.
我...
I...
爸 爸 爸  爸
Dad? Dad? Dad?! Dad!
父亲生病时 家族建议
While Dad is ill, the family proposes
肯德尔掌管公司 罗曼做首席运营官
that Kendall run the company with Roman as COO.
我很严肃的哦
Yes. Very serious.
我没有说我会当一个更好的总裁 我没说
I'm not saying I would make a better CEO. That's unsaid.
你说你没说的时候就是说了
It's not unsaid when you say it.
-你知不知道他给了我份工作  -我怎么会知道
- You know that he gave me a job? - Why would I know?
因为大家谈话的时候可能会提到我
'Cause I thought everybody might be talking about me.
是 大家无时无刻不谈论着你 格雷格表侄
Yeah, no. Everyone was only talking about you, Cousin Greg.
来找我 我会罩着你
Come in and see me, and I'll look after you.
我们面临巨大的债务问题 30亿 别跳楼
There's a huge debt problem. Three billion. Don't jump.
我有个主意 你给我40亿怎么样
I've had an idea. You give me $4 billion.
我还当老板 你来投资
I stay boss, and you invest.
我都不知道你来了
I didn't know you were coming in.
我只想确保你不会
Just making sure you're not selling
在我不知情的情况下卖掉更多公司股份
any more of the company from under me.
爸不太好
Dad's not well.
如果他不小心 就会毁了公司
If he's not careful, he's gonna destroy the company.
让他尊重你的唯一办法 就是尽全力摧毁他
The only way he'll respect you is if you try to destroy him.
我爱我的父亲 但他现在的身体状况
I love my father, but he is currently unfit
不再适合管理公司 我希望可以
to run this company, and I'm calling for a vote
对他总裁和主席的身份进行不信任投票
of no confidence in him as CEO and chairman.
一通屁话 不行
Bullshit. No.
请所有赞成...
All in favour...
你最好想想清楚 罗慕路斯
You better be smelling your fucking armpit, Romulus.
反对投票
Against.
你去哪儿了
Where you been?
我去参加了一场前途光明的面试
Meeting about a prospective job.
帮你爸的敌人干活
With your father's enemy?
你真的想和你的家人开战吗
You want this enough to go to war with your family.
是桑迪 他想吃掉你的那杯羹
It's Sandy. He wants your piece of pie.
拉我进去 我们得体地办好这事
Bring me in. We do this properly.
接手大权 杠杆收购 恶意的
Takeover. Leverage buyout. Hostile.
你的目标是什么
What's your end?
当总裁
CEO.
我想好好谈谈你的事
I want to talk about you properly.
回来吧 我一直觉得你是最聪明的
Come in. I've always thought you were the smartest.
所以你就先给了肯德尔和罗曼机会吗
Oh, so that's why you tried Kendall and Roman first?
你为什么神经兮兮的 小肯
Why are you so jumpy about this, Ken?
为什么神经兮兮
Why am I jumpy?
还不是因为该死的罗曼 该死的小西和康纳
Fucking Rome, fuckin' Shiv and Connor.
还不是因为要让公司脱离家族掌控
About taking the company out of family control.
你他妈在跟我玩熊抱吗
Is this a fuckin' bear hug?
给我滚
Fuck off.
你不会正好认识药贩子[毒品贩子]吧
You don't have a connection for some powder?
认识
Yeah.
小心
Look out!
这可能是你人生的决定性时刻
This could be the defining moment of your life.
富家子弟杀人
A rich kid kills a boy.
你会永远无法翻身
You'd never be anything else.
或者 也可以什么都没发生
Or you could be nothing at all.
你是我儿子 我最棒的儿子
You're my boy, my number one boy.
对不起 先生 罗伊先生
Excuse me, sir? Mr. Roy?
嗯 您能跟我来一下吗
Um, could you come with me, please?
什么事
What is it?
有人...有一位先生找您
We were asked... There's, um, a gentleman here for you.
找我吗...
For me? W...
怎...怎么回事 你什么意思
W... What is this? What do you mean?
我接到的指示是这样
This came as an instruction to me,
所以 您能跟我来一下吗
so could you just come with me please?
嘿 嗨 肯德尔 我是拉格纳·马格鲁森
Hey. Hi, Kendall. I'm Ragnar Magnusson.
-噢...你好  -你好吗
- Oh... Hi. - How are you?
嗨 呃...什么情况
Hi, uh... what is this?
呃...你能先换身衣服吗 然后我们聊聊
Uh... Do you want to get dressed and we can talk?
我们可能要带你出去
We might need to pull you out.
带我出去
Pull me out?
对不起 谁...谁...谁是"我们"
I'm sorry, who... wh... who is "we"?
-你哪位  -没事 肯德尔 我是拉格纳
- Who are you? - It's fine, Kendall. I'm Ragnar.
我和伦敦的平克斯集团有关系
I have relationship with Pinks in London
你父亲要我们
and your father has asked us
尽快让你上电视
to manage getting you on television as soon as possible.
嗯 好的
Uh-huh. Okay.
我才到这里两天的样子 呃...
I've only been here like 48 hours and, uh...
我打算做一个硅土 呃 泥疗 我能不能 呃...
I'm meant to have a silica, uh, mud treatment. Can I just, uh...
呃...不行
Uh... No.
对不起 这样不行
I'm sorry. It's not going to work.
那
So,
看上去桑迪 斯图威 和梅斯贝里资本
it was felt Sandy, Stewy and Maesbury Capital
打算在没有你的情况下继续他们的出价
wouldn't proceed with their bid without you,
但是 他们的熊抱策略已经公开了
but they have gone public with the bear hug,
我们的建议是 让你今天早上在纽约开市之前
and the advice was we should get you on TV this morning
上电视 明白吗
as New York opens. Okay?
好的 明白
Okay. Right.
嗯 但是...会有帮助吗
Um, but will... will that help?
公开的个人退出声明
A public and personal declaration of withdrawal
真的会很有帮助
could be really helpful.
你没事吧 伙计
You okay, mate?
没事
Yeah.
嗯 你可以做到
Yeah, you could do this.
你可以阻止这次熊抱
You could stop it.
好的
Okay, yeah.
我的意思是 要是我爸要我这样做
I mean, if my dad wants me to do it,
呃 我会...我会做的
uh, I'll... I'll do it.
我见过他们的计划 我父亲的计划更好
I saw their plan; Dad's plan is better.
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
你看起来挺不错
You look good.
是的 我感觉 呃 我感觉很好
Yeah, I feel, uh, I feel good.
很好
Great.
还好吧
Good?
嗨
Hi!
嗨 卡洛丽娜 很高兴见到你
Hi, Karolina. Good to see you.
嘿 肯
Hey, Ken.
那 我们有一个附属的Flash工作室
So, we've got a flash studio with an affiliate.
我们给你准备了化妆师和西装
We have hair and make-up and a suit for you.
你没事吧 肯
You okay, Ken?
呃 是的 没事
Uh, yep. Okay.
好的
Okay.
他们会问一些很让人为难的问题 所以我们过一遍问题
They will wanna go for the tough one, so let's run it.
好吗  "那 你和
Okay? "So, um, you allied
你父亲最讨厌的其中一个商业竞争对手结盟
with one of your father's bitterest business rivals
参与了一个可能会让他失去公司的收购计划
in a maneuver that could see him lose the firm.
你为什么要这么做
Why did you do that?
以及你为什么改变主意...
and why did you change your mind...
...退出计划"
... and pull out?"
好的 那
Okay, so then,
你这样回答 "我见过他们的计划 但是 我父亲的计划更好 "
Kendall: "I saw their plan, but Dad's plan was better."
对吧
Right?
对吗 肯德尔
Right, Kendall?
-对吗  -嗯 是的 我知道了
- Right? - Uh-huh. Yeah. I got it.
我要取消这次活动
I'm pulling this.
-不 我可以的 我没问题  -也许我们可以到达以后
- Uh-huh. No, I got it. I got it. - Maybe we'll do something
-在友好媒体做点宣传  -我知道了 我没问题
- with friendly print on arrival. - I got it. I'm good.
嗯 肯 对不起 请给我们拿一张纸巾 好吗
Um, Ken? Excuse me, can we get a tissue, please?
他需要一张纸巾
He needs a tissue.
小心衬衫
Just watch the shirt.
卡洛丽娜 我能做到的 好吗
Karolina, I can do this, okay?
卡洛丽娜 我没事
Karolina, I'm okay.
嗨 肯德尔 还有十秒钟
Hi, Kendall? Ten seconds.
你和萨莎开始的时候 我会给你提示 好吗
I'll red-light you once you're on with Sacha, okay?
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
我们现在邀请了肯德尔·罗伊
We're joined now by Kendall Roy,
他最近和私募股权基金
who was recently allied to a proposed bid
梅斯贝里资本结盟 提出一项报价
by private equity fund Maesbury
试图从他父亲
to take control of Waystar Royco
媒体界传奇人物 洛根·罗伊手中
out of the hands of his own father,
接管韦斯达·罗伊科集团
media legend Logan Roy.
现在 肯德尔 你知道我会问你这个问题
Now, Kendall, you know I'm gonna ask you this,
你和你父亲之间的情况怎么样了
how are things between you and your dad?
呃 非常好
Uh, pretty good.
你知道 我们...我们是 呃 我们...我们非常亲近 所以
You know, we're... we're, uh, we're... we're pretty close, so,
你知道 我们之间就是这样
you know, that's how we are.
哦 嗯 ​​这...
Oh, well, that's a...
-我们采取...抱歉  -...这样挺好
- We take the... Sorry. - ... great attitude.
-对不起 继续吧  -不...哦...好的
- Sorry. Go ahead. - No... O... Okay.
那 我们问深入点 告诉我们发生了什么
So, let's dive in. Tell us what happened.
-好的  -你为什么会参与
- Right. - Why did you get involved?
为什么又退出
Why did you back out?
对 嗯...
Right. Um...
我的意思是 有 呃...
I mean, there's a, uh...
无数的因素 影响着决定
myriad, uh, factors in a decision.
一个瞬间可以决定人的一生
A whole lifetime can lead to a moment,
呃 当我...当我坐下来认真看...
and, uh, when I... when I sat down and really looked...
天啊 他看起来糟透了
God, he looks terrible.
就像一具...湿透的尸体
He's like a... sweaty corpse.
是啊
Yeah.
他看起来就像蜡像 就像一根没刮胡子的蜡烛
He looks waxy, like an unshaven candle.
呃 但我的意思是 嗯...
Uh, but I mean, um...
你知道吗 总结起来就是 我...
You know, the long and the short of it is, I...
见过他们的计划 但是 我父亲的计划更好
saw their plan, and my dad's plan was better.
是这样的 这 这对我和我的家人来说都很难
Look, this is, uh, this is tough for me and my family.
但我对这个行业和公司的发展轨迹
But I made an assessment looking at the sector
进行了评估
and the firm's trajectory
你知道吗 股东们被忽视了
that, you know, shareholders were being ignored.
但事实是 这些担心正在得到解决
But the fact is, those concerns are being addressed,
而且 呃 你知道吗 这...归根结底是股东价值
and, uh, you know, it... it... it comes down to shareholder value.
嗯 你知道的...
Um, and, you know...
...坦率地说 同样显而易见的是
... frankly, uh, what also sort of become obvious,
有一些不可靠的人物也参与了
was there were some unstable personalities involved
这笔交易
uh, with this deal.
"噢 我是肯德尔 我是个时髦的小婊子 "
"Ooh, I'm Kendall and I'm a sassy little bitch."
-你觉得怎么样  -这是怎么回事
- What do you think? - What's going on?
我以为他被打入冷宫了
I thought he was benched.
啊 什么...他在说什么 我们这Wi-Fi烂死了
Ah, what the... What's he saying? We got shitty Wi-Fi.
他看起来很奇怪 对吗
He looks weird, right?
他看起来有点精神错乱 他为什么这么油光水亮的
He looks demented. Why is he so shiny?
为什么你的Wi-Fi很烂
Why do you have shitty Wi-Fi?
我们想找一个不被打扰的地方
We wanted a place without Wi-Fi.
我的意思是 在我看来 他看起来就他妈像个玩笑
I mean, to me he looks like a fucking joke,
但是 普通人会怎么想呢
but what would an average Joe think?
喂 我再打给你
Hey, I'll call you back.
所以 很早之前
So, once upon a time,
传言说 你是继承你父亲位置的
word was that you were in pole position
主力选手 对吗
to take over, right?
而且 呃 但愿你父亲明天不会被公交车撞到
And, uh, God forbid your dad was hit by a bus tomorrow,
你们有接班计划吗
is there a plan?
呃 这个 嗯...我会说...
Uh, well, um... I would say...
计划将会是纽约市政府
uh, the plan would be for the Municipality of New York
得再找一辆公共汽车
to, uh, find another bus,
因为 如果我父亲明天被公交车撞到了
because if my dad gets hit by a bus tomorrow,
这个城市倒下的将会是一辆公共汽车
the city will be down one bus,
而不是一个总裁
not one CEO.
说得好 有道理 肯...
Fair enough. Fair enough, Ken...
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
这是我儿子有生以来
the first fucking thing
做对的他妈的第一件事
my son's ever done right in his life.
继     承
第 二 季  第１集
啊 勇士就这样陨落了
Ah, how the mighty are fallen.
他曾经万人之上 看看他现在
He was a king once. Now look at him.
赤着泥脚 吃着狗屎 成了一头他妈的阉狗
Eating shit with feet of clay, a fucking neutered hound-dog.
我觉得他做得不错
I think he did okay.
哦 是的 他做得很好 他做得还不错
Oh, yes, he did great. He did just fine.
但是 天啦 猫王在他妈的厕所里拉宿便
But, Jesus! Elvis on the fucking toilet!
他不会就这样卷土重来的
Like, he doesn't come back from this,
对吧
right?
就像他只是在纽约证券交易所转了一圈
Like, he just walked around the New York Stock Exchange
手里拿着被阉割的鸡巴
with his severed dick in his hand
问哪里可以领到免费汤
asking where was good for free soup.
他刚刚吃了条狗鸡巴 把狗骨头吮吸干净了
He just ate the big dog dick. Sucked that pooch bone dry!
亲爱的 有什么反应 股价怎么样了
Honey, what's the reaction? What happened to the price?
呃 下跌了 又反弹了
Uh, dropped down, shot back up.
我觉得桑迪和斯图威给爸爸提供了一条出路 资产交换
I think Sandy and Stewy offer Dad a way out, asset swap.
对吧 我的意思是 下一步动作就是这个了
Right? I mean, that's what the next move is.
嗯 我会这么认为 对吧
Yeah, I would think so, right?
-如果他们要继续的话  -是啊
- If they're going to proceed. - Well,
-他们不能变得敌对  -对
- they can't go hostile. - No.
尤其是没有肯德尔的股权的情况下
Especially without Kendall's equity.
我操 是啊
Shit. No.
你想取消蜜月吗
You wanna abandon honeymoon?
不 我的意思是...不 我不想 你呢
No, I mean... No, I don't want to. Do you?
不 我不想 不想
No. I don't want to. No.
你呢
Do you?
你帮我准备摩托车了吗
Did you get the bike?
有 但是你父亲不希望你一个人骑 肯
Yeah, your dad didn't want you to ride all alone, Ken.
我们安排了一个人
We got a guy.
噢 他来了 洋芋头先生
Oh, here he is! Mr. Potato Head!
我的塑料对手
My plastic adversary.
欢迎来到地堡
Welcome to the bunker.
向咕噜兽们问好
Say hello to the grunts.
-无意冒犯 卡尔  -没有冒犯
- No offense, Karl. - None taken.
好吧 有点冒犯 卡尔
Yeah, well, a bit of offense, Karl,
因为聪明点的首席财务官早就应该预见到
because a smarter CFO might have seen
这场他妈的灾难会到来
this fucking disaster coming.
明白了 好的 现在觉得冒犯了
Got it. Yep. Offense now taken.
谢谢你上电视
Thank you for the TV thing.
嗯...这是我至少能做到的事
I mean... You know, the least I could do.
价格只上涨了一点点 所以我认为 这对我们没有任何帮助
Price is up a little, so I don't think it's done anything for us.
好吧 至少他努力了
Well, at least he tried.
好了 卡尔 我要给这个两面派简单介绍下情况
Okay, Karl, I need to De-brief the double agent.
震地者们可以散场了[游戏星际之剑]
The ground pounders can fuck off.
好的 我会准备好投资者电话清单
All right, I'll get the investor call list
之后要用 还有 ...
for later, and...
我会 我会在20分钟后向你汇报最新情况...
I'll, uh, update you in, what, 20, on the...
不不不 你留下来
No, no, no. You're staying.
留下来
Stay.
好了 轮到你了 踏上拷问台吧
Okay. Now you. Step up onto the rack.
我会像僵尸皮纳塔一样一块一块地扯断你的肢体
I'm gonna pull you limb from limb like a piñata,
看看会掉些什么出来
see what falls out.
好的 那 你想要...什么
Okay, so, you want... what?
我想要他们的计划 他们的时间表是怎么安排的
I want their game plan. What their timetable is,
资本结构 怎么收官 他们可能会接受什么条件
the capital structure. Endgame. What they might accept.
他们的弱点是什么 但是 我们先从头开始
What their weak points are. But we'll start at the start.
他们是什么时候接近你的
When did they approach you?
嗯 他们什么时候接近我的
Um, when did they approach me?
嗯 他们花了很长时间
Mm-hmm. Did it take long
还是说第一次联系你 你就投降了
or did you open your legs on the first date?
好吧 不 他们花了很多时间
Well, no, they took a fair time
来说服我 要我 呃...
to persuade me to, uh...
背叛我
Betray me.
-是的  -嗯 那很好
- Yeah. - Well, that's nice.
听着 你想了解整件事的
Look, do you want the psychodrama
心理过程还是...
of the whole thing, or... ?
他们认为我会怎么应对
What do they think I'll do?
这个 呃 斯图威认为你可能会谈判
Well, uh, Stewy thinks you might come to the table.
桑迪认为你会很敌对
Sandy thinks it will be hostile.
他们认为他们会赢吗
They think they'll win?
是啊 我们...他们...他们觉得 呃...
Yeah. We... They... They think, uh...
我估计 当我谈到公司的内部情况的时候...
I guess when I talked about inside the firm...
...呃 他们有这样一个印象
... uh, they got the impression
觉得公司里有一些不稳定的决策
that there was some erratic decision-making.
他们认为你情绪化 不稳定
They think you're emotional, unstable,
做决策没有逻辑
not necessarily logic driven,
越来越弱 而且你会在压力下崩溃
getting weaker and you'll crack under pressure.
他们在拉拢谁
And who are they hitting?
显然是那些大股东
Obviously, major shareholders.
正如你所料 大多数机构都会规避风险
Most institutional are, as you'd expect, risk averse
而你的遗产信托很大程度上
and there's a big degree of sort of legacy trust in you
就像一个一次性的巫毒教
as a kind of one-shot voodoo guy
把所有的事情都联系在了一起
who holds the whole thing together.
就这些吗
That it?
听着 我要 呃...
Look, let me, uh...
我要去 呃...
I'm going to, uh...
准备那些电话清单了 好吗
get those call lists, huh?
我和他们的公关团队谈过 呃...
Yeah, I talked to their PR team and, uh...
我把你正在服用的药物名称告诉他们了
I gave them what medications you're on.
他们知道你打艾弗森
And they have for background you hitting Iverson.
他们知道你在我办公室的地毯上撒尿
And they have you pissing on the floor of my office.
听着 爸爸 显然 我 呃...
Listen, Dad, obviously, I'm, uh...
我...我觉得很糟糕 我只是想说...
I... I feel awful, and I just wanna say...
好了 你滚蛋吧 他们会把你安置在某个地方的
Fine. Well, fuck off. They'll put you somewhere.
投资人的要求
Investor calls.
在收购计划上给我来点有用的 好吗
Pour me some buckets of cold shit on the bid, all right?
那
So,
保罗有一份我们希望你能联络的
Paul has the list of the top ten shareholders
前十大股东的名单
that we'd like you to hit
他会告诉你所有的台词 然后...
and he'll talk you through all the lines and...
-好吗  -好的
- Okay? - Okay.
-行  -嗯 好的
- All right. - Yup. Okay.
呃 听着 卡罗丽娜 杰西回来了吗
Um, listen, Karolina. Is Jess back?
没有 但我们可以联系杰西
Uh, no, but we can reach out to Jess.
嗯 在某些事情上 通常是
Yeah, just normally on, uh, on some matters,
杰西代表我 和我的朋友尼克对话
Jess speaks to, um, my friend Nick for me.
而且 他为我提供消息来源
And, uh, he sources for me.
嗯 对
Right.
是的 我...我...我需要 嗯...
Yeah, I... I... I need, um...
我...看 我...我要清理我带来的后果
I... Look, I'm... I'm going to be cleaning up my act.
-你知道吗 我一直都在这么做  -嗯嗯
- You know, I have been. - Mm-hmm.
但是 老实说 我现在需要一个帮我矫正的人
But, honestly, right now, I need a straightener.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道吗 我 嗯...
You know, I, um...
我很失望 这次突袭 我没有得到任何提前警告
I was quite disappointed I didn't get any advance warning
杰米 这非常令人失望
of this attack, Jamie. That's quite disappointing.
我的银行家怎么会不知道
How does my banker not know?
桑迪很厉害 他的操作滴水不漏
Sandy's tough, and his operation's a steel box.
没有人知道
Nobody knew.
那 你准备怎么出招
So, uh, what's your move?
我准备怎么出招
What's my move?
看看我他妈给你准备的葡萄酒
Look at the fucking wine I'm serving you.
我他妈正在和你一起喝酒吃饭呢
I'm fucking wining and dining you.
我准备怎么出招 我的意思是 我不知道 我猜...
What's my move? I mean, I don't know. I guess...
很显然 呃 我会说我正在思考
the obvious, uh, I'll say I'm thinking,
然后拖一段时间 希望计划胎死腹中 呃...
and, uh, drag it out, hope that it dies, uh...
指定一个接班人
Name a successor.
那样可能是个好招
That could be good.
指定谁呢
Who?
嗯 这就有点复杂了
Well, that's a bit complicated.
我还有什么资源 可以拿来防守
What else I got? On the defense.
这个 很难防守
Well, that's, uh, difficult.
我他妈得付你多少钱才能让你说点实质性的东西
How much do I have to fucking pay you to say something?
听着 你不想卖公司
Look, you don't want to sell,
你不想卖 你根本不想卖
you don't wanna sell, you don't wanna sell.
那我还有什么余地告诉你一些你不想听的话
So where's my margin to tell you something you don't wanna hear?
好吧 就把这想象成我对你的信任的
Well, try to think of it as a long-term investment
长期投资
in my trust in you.
行 老实说 就商业基本面来看
All right. In all honesty, on the business fundamentals,
你应该和他们做交易 把公司卖掉
you should make a deal and sell.
如果你不这样做 那将是一场恶战
If you don't, it's going to be a vicious fight.
可能会持续数月 数年
It could extend to months, years.
也许你最后会赢 只是也许
Perhaps you win. Perhaps.
但是 在赢之前 什么事都干不成
But till then, nothing will get done.
还会占用你所有的资源
It'll soak up all of your resources,
所有的注意力
all of your attention,
用你拥有的每一个管理
beating them away with every regulatory,
财务和政治方面的武器去打败他们
financial and political weapon that you have at your disposal.
水里面混进了杂质
There's blood in the water,
而且你们的股价也在逐渐下降
and your price is edging down.
科技即将到来 科技已经到来
Tech is coming. Tech is here.
科技的双手扼住了你的喉咙
Tech has its hands around your throat.
可能会有一两个传统媒体运营
There's maybe one, two legacy media operations
能够让自己扩张到足以生存
that will make themselves big enough to survive.
桑迪的报价虚高了
The price that Sandy's offering is inflated.
价格虚高是因为痛苦 自我和怨恨
It's inflated by bitterness, ego and spite.
你选择不卖
You choose not to sell,
好吧 两年 四年后会有什么不同
well, what's going to be different in two, four years?
事情会改变吗
Are things gonna change?
会有更多人阅读你的报纸吗
More people gonna read your newspapers?
大家还看电视吗
Watch TV?
无论是文化上 结构上还是经济上
Culturally, structurally and financially,
你都一团泥沼
you're in the toilet.
五年后 你会变成大型泥沼
In five years, you'll be in the mega toilet.
明智的做法是卖掉公司
The wise thing to do is to sell.
一般来说 你做的是明智之举
Now, generally, you do the wise thing.
但是 不 不 显然这一次你并不明智
But no, no, obviously not this time.
这一次 你...你会骂我是恶心的东西
This time you'll... you'll call me something disgusting
然后愤怒地往墙上摔碎醒酒器
and throw a decanter at the wall.
就这次调查而言...
In terms of this investigation...
...我们将调查这次爆炸事故发生的过程与原因
... we will explore how and why this occurred.
我们计划进行有史以来最彻底的
and we plan for the most thorough internal investigation
内部调查
ever seen.
有个问题请问罗曼·罗伊
Uh, one for Roman Roy.
调查什么时候开始
When will the investigation start,
以及有什么可能的原因吗
and any issues that are looking like likely causes?
那 关于调查的时间 马上就会开始
Well, on, uh, on the timing? Right away.
我们非常重视这一点
We take this incredibly seriously.
嗯 至于...
Um, and as for, um...
呃 至于事故原因的确定
Uh, as for determination of the cause,
我们只是不想推测
we just don't wanna speculate.
而且我不想开玩笑
And I don't wanna be facetious,
但是 莎拉 在这个问题上 我不是火箭科学家
but, Sarah, on that point, I'm not a rocket scientist.
那好吧 佐藤主任 还有一个问题
All right then. Director Sato, one more question:
韦斯达·罗伊科是否准备好了...
Is Waystar Royco ready...
...承担责任
... to accept liability?
是否会有财务上的拨款
Will there be a financial settlement
提供给受害者家属
offered to the victims' families?
呃 对此我非常抱歉
Uh, I'm very sorry for this.
例如...
For example...
天哪 你收到信息了吗 你收到这个了吗
Holy shit. Did you get the text? Did you get this?
-这是真的吗  -是的 我收到了
- Is this for real? - Yeah, I got it.
-要卖吗  -他不会卖的 对吧
- Sell? - He wouldn't, would he?
汤姆
Tom.
天哪 他说他要卖公司
Holy shit. He's saying he's selling?
那...
That's...
他永远不会卖的 对吧 我们要回去吗
He would never sell, would he? Do we go?
呃 应该回去吧
Uh, I guess?
但是 他妈的 婚礼和蜜月都被他搞砸了
But, fuck! The wedding and the honeymoon fucked?
真是个疯狂的混蛋
What a nutty bastard!
真他妈是个自我为中心的老白毛
What a fucking egocentric great white!
操他妈的
Motherfucker.
房子不错 伙计
Nice abode, man.
你还好吗
You okay?
呃 有...有什么新鲜事吗
Uh, what's... what's the news?
发生...发生什么了
What's... what's going on?
你好吗
How you doin'?
嗯 一切都很好 挺好 伙计
Yeah, all good. It's good, dude?
你这房子太酷了
This place is sick!
哦 对 现在是时装周 所有好的顶层公寓都没了
Oh, yeah. It's fashion week; all the good penthouses are gone.
嗯 不 我的意思是 我肯定...这...是的 可能有更好的
Yeah, no, I mean I'm sure... It... Yeah, could be way better.
我只是...不...知道还要怎么好
I just... don't... know how.
你的...你的...你自己的房子怎么了
What, uh... What's uh... What happened with your house?
哦 我...我 我把它卖掉了
Oh, I'm... I'm, uh, I got rid of it.
里面有拉瓦的气息
It smelt of Rava.
哦 伙计 是的
Oh, dude, yeah.
你带了那个...
Did you bring, uh...
-哦 是的 是的  -太棒了
- Oh, yeah, yeah. - Great.
呃 这是"教练"那里买的吗
Uh, did this come from Coach?
哦 不 他出城了 这是另外一个人那里搞的
Oh, no, uh, he's out of town. That is from another source.
呕 老兄...你从哪里搞的这个
Eww. Dude. W... Where did you get this?
呃 这个吗 我...从另外一个贩子那里买的
Uh, that? It... It's from a connection.
公园里的
In the park.
-公园可卡因  -是的
- Park coke? - Yeah.
给我吸公园可卡因 你他妈跟我开玩笑吧
I'm doing park coke? Are you fucking kidding me?
太他妈"完美"了
That is just perfect.
等我吸完了 我他妈的鼻孔还在 那就真是走运了
I'll be lucky if I have any fucking nostrils left after this.
要是我的鼻隔掉下来了 我会让你吃了它
If my septum falls out, I'm gonna make you eat my septum.
嗯 这家伙...这家伙有...有好货
Yeah, this guy's... this guy's got... got the good shit.
真的
Yeah.
如何 好...
How is it? Is it...
还是不好...
Is it not...
嗯 不好 是我吸过的最烂的可卡因
Mm, yeah, no, that's the worst coke I've ever had.
不 伙计...
No, dude...
伙计 我很抱歉
Dude, I'm so sorry.
他向我保证过
Like, he promised me.
哦 他向你保证过吗
Oh, he promised you?
我发誓 我的意思是 我...你想要我把它退回去吗
I swear. I mean, I... Do you want me to take it back?
是的 拿回去退钱 格雷格
Yeah, take it back for a refund, Greg!
你知道吗 你...你保留收据了吗
You know, did you... did you keep the receipt?
去退吧...去...拿回去退钱
Go get... go... Go take it back for a refund.
他要去夏宫度假
He's opening the summer palace
以避开峰会 全家人都要去
to keep the summit out of view. It's the full fuckin' number.
好的 那咱们地狱见 老哥
Okay. Yeah, well, I'll see you at the hellhole, bro.
粪坑见 老妹
See you at the shitpit, sis.
哦 欢迎 抱歉
Oh, welcome! Apologies.
我们会尽快把一切
We'll have everything straight
-都安排好...  -哦 不 是我来早了
- just as soon as... - Oh, no, I'm early.
没事 别担心 只管 继续做你们的 就当我没在这儿
It's good. don't worry. Just, uh, carry on. I'm not here.
这是什么...
What is the... ?
对不起 气味很糟糕 我们正在处理
Sorry about the smell. We're working on that.
老天 太...难闻了
God, that's... bad.
这他妈是什么
What the fuck is that?
我们不能让窗户一直开着
We can't exactly keep the windows open.
你试过香薰蜡烛吗
Have you tried scented candles?
-嘿 你怎么样啊 性感美女  -嘿 罗曼
- Hey, what up sex pot? - Hey, Rome.
-这是什么臭味  -我知道
- What is that stink? - I know.
死孩子埋在浅坟里了还是怎么回事
Dead kid shallow grave somewhere or what?
嘿 你想呼吸点新鲜空气吗
Hey, do you wanna get some air?
当然
Yes.
-你理发了  -是的
- You got a haircut. - Yeah.
-难看死了  -那是因为这发型很时尚
- I hate it. - That's because it's stylish.
我担心老家伙会很兴奋
I'm worried slash excited
万一他真他妈的杀了肯德尔呢
in case he actually fucking kills Kendall.
我的意思是 他可能会杀了他
I mean, he might kill him.
他可以去找他 可以杀了他
Could go for him. He could kill him.
老天 如果爸杀了他就太奇怪了
Man, it'd be so weird if he killed him.
所以 这对你有好处 对吧
So this is good for you, right?
什么 你是说卖掉公司吗
What, if he sells?
他不会卖的
He's not gonna sell.
嗯 我不知道
Hmm, I don't know about that.
好吧 肯德尔永远出局了 对吗
Well, Kendall's out for good, right?
对他来说 最好的情况是
Best case for him is
爸爸让他干一个星期 搅黄这个收购计划
Dad keeps him on for like a week to kill the deal,
然后他就彻底没戏了
then he's pure carcass.
我和吉尔是一边的
I'm with Gil.
康纳...
Connor's...
我的意思是 我操 康纳将会进白宫
I mean, fuck, Connor's gonna be in the White House.
嗯 当然...
Yeah, sure...
可能吧 我的意思是 我没有考虑过 但...
I guess. I mean, I hadn't considered it, but...
哦 你没考虑过吗
Oh, you hadn't considered?
嗯 不 我...我觉得 理论上 是没考虑过
Well, no, I... I guess, theoretically, yeah.
这是个很棒的时刻 对吧 祝你好运
It's a cool moment. Hm? Good luck.
怎么了
What?
-怎么了...  -我知道你在做什么
- Wha... - I know what you're doing.
我...我只是说 这很令人兴奋 一切都准备好了
I... I'm just saying it's exciting. It's all set.
当然
Sure.
你在逗我玩
You're fucking with me.
-但是我无所谓  -罗曼 我不是在逗你
- But I'm impervious. - Rome, I'm not fucking with you.
-我只是说 祝你好运  -好吧 非常感谢
- I'm just saying good luck. - Great. Well, thanks a lot.
什么
What?
你想干扰我的思想 不过 这样很好
You're trying to get inside my head, but that's cool,
我可以应付
I can cope.
怎么了 也许我他妈的准备好了
What, maybe I'm fuckin' ready for it.
-你是准备好了  -是的
- You are. - Yeah.
我的意思是 你有的是搞砸的机会
I mean, there's always room for you to blow up.
我的意思是...
I mean...
没有人提到过搞砸
nobody mentioned blowing up,
然后你突然提到搞砸
and then suddenly you mention blowing up?
那现在怎么样 我应该担心他妈的搞砸吗
And now what? I'm supposed to worry about fucking blowing up?
我不认为你会搞砸
I don't think you're gonna blow up.
我...
I'm...
罗曼 我认为你是一个超有才的超级明星
Rome, I think you're a super-talented superstar,
而且我...我爱你
and I... I love you.
哦 你他妈太婊了
Oh, you're such a fucking bitch.
所以 你不知道是什么气味吗
So you don't know what it is?
我们正在再一次四处巡查
We're looking absolutely everywhere once again.
那现在的返修都可以了吗
And all is well now with the renovation?
是的 那些都解决好了
Yes, all that was resolved.
把门都打开
Open the doors.
闻起来就像奶酪贩子死了
It smells like the cheesemonger died
然后把鸡鸡掉在奶酪上了一样臭
and left his dick in the Brie.
我需要呼吸新鲜空气
I need to breathe.
肯德尔
Kendall!
来吧 我们把臭味源头找出来
Come on! Let's hunt this out!
你知道吗 你...实际上 你得习惯这种气味
You know, you... you get used to it, actually.
价值两亿的房子...
Yeah, 200 million...
我得用个夹子夹住鼻子才不会呕出来
and I need a clip on my nose to stop me fucking retching.
你想谈谈莱尔德的想法吗
You wanna talk about Laird's idea?
不 晚点再说
Nah. Later.
那 听着
So, listen.
-嗯  -你没事吧
- Hm? - You all right?
是啊 是的 我 非常好
Yeah. Yeah, I'm um, pretty good.
我...我可以在某些时候休息一下...
I... I could use some downtime at... at some point, to...
是的 当然 当然 只不过 不要低沉 知道吗...
Yeah, sure, sure. Just don't, um, you know...
你知道 胡思乱想很自然...
You know, uh, thinking's natural...
但是毫无用处 你知道...在有限的情况下
can't be helped, but, you know... in limits.
对 确实 是的
Right. Exactly. Right.
好了 真好 把一切都说出来真好
Well, good. Good to have it all out.
科林
Colin!
你得和科林谈谈
You should have to with Colin.
一切都好吗
Everything is good?
-嗯  -是吗
- Mm. - Yeah?
-肯德尔 - 嗨 玛西娅
- Kendall. - Hi, Marcia.
你怎么样
Ça Va?
旅途怎么样
How was your trip?
很好 挺好的
It was good. It was fine.
没有任何意外 没有任何小插曲吗
No accidents? No hiccups?
嗯 没有 没有小插曲
Uh, no. No hiccups.
我知道 你经历了一段困难时期
Je sais. You've been through difficult times.
你是个好孩子
You're a nice boy.
但是 艰难困苦出能人 对吧
But out of difficult times come strong men, right?
玛丽安 请把蜡烛拿出来
Marianne, come up with the candles, please.
肯
Ken.
有空吗
Got a minute?
嗯
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
那 我不知道你知道多少或者想知道多少
So, I don't know how much you know or care to know,
但是 你爸想让我跟你谈谈
but your dad wanted me to offer to talk you through things.
哦 好的
Oh, okay.
所以 我就直说了
So, I'll just lay it out for you?
哦 好的 我的意思是...
Oh, yeah, okay. I mean...
我不需要...
I don't need...
是吗 好吧 我开说了 这样你好记住
Yeah? Well, shall I, just so you know?
那 撞车现场是凌晨4点左右被发现的
So, the site of the crash was discovered around 4:00 a.m.
是我们的两个人看到了破坏的篱笆
by two of our guys who saw the busted fence
-然后跟着查看发现的  -嗯
- and followed that up. - Uh-huh.
然后他们通知了当地警方
And they informed local police.
如你所知
And as you know,
有人发现了一张门禁卡 然后已经交给我了
an entry keycard was found and passed to me.
那个人是我们圈子以外的人
So, that's one individual outside of our loop,
但是我认识他 而且我认为他很可靠
but who is known to me and who I consider secure.
好的
Okay.
那天早上 英国警方派出了潜水员
And the UK police sent divers in that morning.
嗯 好
Right. Right.
那个孩子 呃 安德鲁·多兹 很显然 他已经死了
And the kid, uh, Andrew Dodds, well, he was dead obviously.
他没有系好安全带 所以他没能在撞车时
He'd unclipped his seatbelt, so he hadn't survived the impact
幸免于难
to do that.
哦 好的
Oh, okay.
所以 初步判断是他一个人独自驾驶车
So, the initial determination was that he was travelling solo
这一点没有人提出质疑
and that hasn't been challenged.
河岸也因为大雨和我们的人
And the riverbank was also heavily compromised
以及打捞行动遭到严重破坏
by rain and our guys and the salvage operation,
所以 没有其他人出现过在那里的证据
so there were no indicators of another individual.
这就是我们目前的情况
So, that's where we are.
我们希望英国验尸官能够做出结论
We expect the UK coroner to deliver a ruling
判定为不幸遇难
of death by misadventure,
如果是这样的话 案子就结了
and that will be it as far as we see.
有什么问题或担心吗
Any questions or concerns?
嗯...应该没有 没有
Um... I do not think so, no.
谢谢你 科林
Thank you, Colin.
好的
Good.
哦 我的天啦
Oh, my God.
看看他
Look at him.
不了 谢谢
No. No thanks.
我觉得我做不到
I don't think I can do this.
好吧 我们应该揍他吗 用棍子或石头
Well, shall we just hit him? With a stick or rocks?
是啊
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
行尸走肉 他妈的尸体醒过来了
Dead man walking. The fucking cadaver awakens.
嘿
Hey.
你什么时候爬进来的
When did you crawl in?
昨天 你呢
Yesterday. You?
那 你跟他谈过话了吗 这是真的吗 他会那样做吗
So, you spoken to him? Is this real? Is he gonna do it?
他要卖公司吗
Is he gonna sell?
呃 我不知道
Uh, I dunno.
哦 你不知道
Oh, you don't know.
那
So?
到底发生什么了 你为什么退出了
What the fuck happened? Why'd you pull out?
我估计 我 呃...
I guess I, uh...
我见过他们的计划
I saw their plan.
你知道的 爸的计划更好
You know, Dad's plan is better.
好吧
Okay.
瞎扯淡 到底发生什么事了
Bullshit. Um, what happened?
我改变了主意吧
I changed my mind, I guess.
去你的 你就不能在我的婚礼之前
Fuck you. And you couldn't have changed your mind
改变主意吗
before my wedding?
你应该很清楚 等你对他不再有用了
You do realize how fucked you're going to be
你的处境会有多惨 对吧
as soon as you're no longer any use to him, right?
他让你在电视上喝下了他妈的
He's got you eating fucking humiliation gumbo
屈辱浓汤 然后呢
on TV, and then what?
没错 爸会给你演奏一首欢快的曲子
Yeah, Dad's gonna play a merry tune on you
然后把你他妈的从窗户扔出去
and then throw you out the fucking window,
你也知道会这样 对吧
and you know that, right?
他就像爸的性爱机器人
He's like a sex robot for Dad to fuck.
他就像一只被痛殴过的老狗
He's like an old beaten dog.
嗯 他两者都是 同时还是一坨狗屎
Well, he's both of those things and also a piece of shit.
你知道吗 他就是一个他妈的可怜的自恋狂
You know, he's a pathetic little fucking narcissist
总是反复强调自己的利益
who repeatedly puts his own self-interest
高于一切
above everything else
然后企图用不称职的残酷的市场筹款努力
and then tries to justify it with half-assed appeals
来证明自己观点的合理性
of the rigors of the fucking market.
你真他妈混蛋
You're a fucking prick.
嗯 也许我就是
Uh-huh. Maybe I am.
哦 拜托 混球 还个嘴啊
Oh, come on, fuck-bag, fight back.
我...伙计们 我...我只是...
I... guys, I... I just...
我不感兴趣
I can't get into it.
哦 你不感兴趣 噢 没劲
Oh, you can't get into it? Uh-huh. Shucks.
去你的 老哥 来啊 跟我们说说
Fuck you, man. Come on. Treat us.
你到底为什么要退出
Why did you actually back out?
对不起 小西 关于你的婚礼
I'm sorry, Shiv, about the wedding.
你怎么有脸向我道歉
How dare you apologize to me?
顺便说一句 你看起来像坨狗屎
You look like shit, by the way.
为什么我们不能把它保留在内部
Why can't we keep it in-house?
我可是花了一大笔钱
It's costing me an arm and a fucking leg.
他们找到气味源头了 你应该来一趟
They have located the source of the smell. You should come.
那 你要告诉我你到底在想什么吗
So, are you going to tell me what you're actually thinking?
都没有定数
Lot of moving parts.
卖公司 是真的吗
The selling, is it real?
我们再看看会怎么发展
We'll see how it goes.
你怎么看
What do you think?
怎么 我也要给你出谋划策了吗
What? I have to dance for the Daddy too?
有人强烈建议我接受这个出价
I've had strong advice to accept the offer.
如果我不知道我在想什么 怎么办
What if I didn't know what I think?
也许你应该卖掉
Maybe you should sell.
你老了 你身体一直都不好
You're old. You've not been well.
好的 很好 谢谢
Okay. Very well. Thank you.
-什么啊  -他妈的...
- What? - Putain De merde...
噢 这他妈的是什么
Oh, what the fuck is that?
把承包商给我叫过来
Oh, I need to see that contractor.
叫他们来这里 他们在这儿吗 来吧 我们开始吧
Get 'em down here. Are they here? Come on, we're starting.
我不想要这些垃圾
And I don't want all this shit.
都在臭味里熏着 比萨 我们要披萨
It's sat around in the stink! Pizza! We'll have pizza!
那么 你觉得是什么把戏 小西
So, what's the game do you reckon, Shiv?
我不知道 宣称他要卖公司 然后看谁叫得最大声
I dunno. Say he's selling and see who squeals loudest?
测试忠诚度 还是生产力头脑风暴
Kind of loyalty test? Or productivity brainstorm?
或者我们把肯德尔杀了 当作披萨上面的配料吃了
Or we kill and eat Kendall as a pizza topping.
嘿 爸爸
Hey, Dad.
威拉 嗨
Willa, hi!
好了 下午好
So! Afternoon.
谢谢大家 都来了
Thank you all for, uh, making it.
我们需要讨论这次熊抱策略
We need to discuss this bear hug.
显然 我有义务为股东们
Obviously, I have obligations to the shareholders
认真考虑一下 哈哈
to seriously consider it. Ha-ha.
现在 肯德尔的退出可能会伤到他们的计划 我们再看看
Now Kendall's row-back may have hurt them, we'll see.
收购计划可能会中止 也可能不会
It may kill the bid, it may not.
但是我猜 我面对的问题是
But I guess the question that that's been put to me is
我们真的想打这场仗吗
do we really want this fight?
或者现在是兑现筹码 离开赌场的时刻了
Or is now the moment to cash in and fuck off out of the casino?
因为 如果我们要打仗
Because if we do fight,
我就得告诉董事会 我希望谁来接班
I need to tell the board who I want to take over.
所以 都说说吧 我希望你们能畅所欲言
So, please. I want you to speak freely.
怎么了
What?
你所说的任何话都将成为呈堂证供
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
哦 说吧 我们都是老熟人了
Oh, come on. We're all pals here.
-哦耶  -都他妈畅所欲言吧
- Oh, yeah. - Let's fuckin' have it out.
我想你应该打一仗 但是 呃...
I think you should fight, but, uh...
我的意思是 这一切都是你建造的
I mean, you're the one who built it all.
你是老大 神话和传奇都是你
You're the man, the myth, the legend.
哇 真动听
Oh, that is adorable.
你总是在找爸爸 不是吗 对吧
You're always looking out for Pops, aren't you, right?
但是 他是在说爸应该打一仗
But is he saying Dad should stay on
因为桑迪和斯图威想要他打一仗吗
because that's what Sandy and Stewy want?
我们怎么知道他不是双重间谍
How do we know he's not a double agent?
很高兴见到你 老康
Nice to see you, Con.
嘿 小肯 我只是把别人的想法说出来而已
Hey, Ken, I'm just saying what others are thinking.
有可能啊
It's possible.
我们应该搜他的身找窃听器吗 还是烧了他 看他是不是巫师
Should we frisk him for a wire? Burn him? See if he's a witch?
他已经自食苦果了
He has taken his medicine.
他已经自食苦果了 是吗
He's taken his medicine? Is that it?
爸 你在古斯塔夫用他妈的拖鞋抽罗曼
Dad, you beat Roman with a fucking slipper
直到他哭着点龙虾 还记得吗
in Gustav till he cried for ordering lobster, remember?
而肯德尔想要毁了你
And Kendall tries to kill you
才被打入冷宫五分钟
and he's five minutes out in the cold?
不是你买单的时候 点菜单上最贵的菜
It is not polite to order the most expensive item on the menu
是很不礼貌的 西沃恩
when you're not paying, Siobhan.
我们现在不是在翻旧账
We're not doing memory lane here.
来吧 都一吐为快吧 你们都怎么想的
Come on, spit it out. What do you all think?
坚持还是卖掉
Stick or sell?
好吧 我认为你正处在人生的黄金时期
Well, I for one think you're in the prime of your life
而且我认为医生会觉得你可以再干十年
and I think another decade is just what the doctor ordered.
一票坚持
That's one stick.
你要我说吗 我觉得 卖掉很不错...
You want me to go? I mean, sell seems cool...
嘿 爸 威拉认为卖掉公司很不错
Hey, Dad, Willa thinks selling seems cool.
混蛋
Asshole.
爸 我觉得 有时候你有可能
Dad, I think it is possible that you have sometimes
多多少少让自由辩论的气氛冷却了
somewhat chilled the atmosphere of free-flowing debate.
你们知道吗 柯达的股票每股曾经达到一百块
You know, Kodak was trading at about a hundred dollars a share
1997年的时候
back in '97.
但是昨天 你可以花大约3块就能买到
Yesterday, you could pick it up at about three bucks.
我们也可能是这样的下场
That could be us.
如果我们现在变现 可以拿走100亿美元
If we cash out, we could walk away with ten billion.
罗曼
Roman.
你怎么看
What do you think?
我不知道 呃 我他妈的爱钱
I dunno. Uh, I fucking love money,
但我真的很害怕你 所以...
but I'm really scared of you, so...
呃 说实话
Uh, honestly, um,
我不确定我是否愿意在公共场合
I'm not sure I'm willing to give my strategic advice
提出我的战略建议 因为我可以
in a public forum when I could be
在未来参与到任何计划里
a player in any future moves.
嗯...爸
Um... Dad?
爸
Dad?
-爸  -他在里面吗
- Dad? - Is he in there?
是的 他进去了
Yeah, he went in there.
一个一个进来 一个接一个
One by one, come in. One by one.
一个接一个吗
One by one?
说真的 搞什么鬼
Seriously, what the fuck?
我不会进去的
I'm not going in there.
好了 现在这里没有其他人
So, now that there's no one here
偷听你的精彩见解了
to hear your wonderful insights,
你怎么看
what do you say?
嗯...好吧...
Um... Okay, um...
爸 我确实对此有个想法
I actually do have a pitch on this, Dad.
金融化
Financialization.
什么热就干什么 我的意思是 保留政治权力方面的新闻
Float hot. I mean, keep news for political power,
用于市场的操纵能力
for market manipulation capability.
但其余的 我们就玩市场游戏
But the rest, we play the markets with.
你和我 在城市上空居高临下
You and me up in a little pod above the city,
玩死那些创业公司和养老基金
fucking start ups and shitting on pension funds.
非常容易操作 高度机动性
Highly maneuverable, highly mobile.
那 除掉桑迪和斯图威方面呢
And in terms of getting rid of Sandy and Stewy?
哦 去他妈的 吓跑他们
Oh, fuck 'em. Scare 'em off.
比如呢
As in?
就像是 你知道的..."狗狗震"里面一样 爸
As in, you know... Scooby Doo it, Dad.
你在主题公园里扮成鬼魂
You just dress up as ghosts in the theme park.
嗯 你懂的 只不过我们是通过律师
Um, you know, we just use the lawyers,
本金和利息 妓女施展美人计
the PIs, the honey-trap hookers,
所有任我们摆布的不讨喜的人来吓跑他们
all the unpleasant people at our disposal.
召集所有的支持力量
Call in all the favors.
他妈的雷森总统
Fucking President Raisin,
所有欠我们情的参议院屌毛
all the Senate cock sucks who owe us.
他妈的干 干 干
Fucking kill, kill, kill.
天啦 小西 他不会真的要卖掉公司吧
Jesus, Shiv, might he actually sell?
你知道吗 这事真的在发生了
You know, it's really happening in there.
这就像和他妈的宙斯玩金罗美一样[一种两人玩的纸牌游戏]
It's like playing fucking Gin Rummy with Zeus.
我不相信卖公司的说法 这是个考验 不是吗
I don't buy the selling. It's a test, no?
谁告诉所罗门不要剥夺孩子的生命
Whoever tell Solomon not to asset-strip
孩子就归谁[所罗门智断亲生子案]
the baby gets to keep the baby.
但是...不能是肯德尔
But it... it can't be Kendall,
-对吧  -是的
- can it? - Yeah.
不 也不会是罗曼
No, it's not gonna be Roman.
汤姆 放轻松点吧
Just take it easy, Tom.
我知道 我...我只是觉得 我们的要求至少是
I know, I ju... I just think the least that we want for me
别再让我负责公园和游轮部门 对吧
is to get me out of parks and cruises, right?
让我掌管类似洛杉矶华伦媒体这样的部门
Into something like heartland media. LA.
掌管一个关键部门 对吧 或者 我们要不要直接问他
One of the key divisions, you know? Or do we ask?
我们要不要直接问一下 我们要不要加快计划
Do we just ask? Do we accelerate the plan?
你知道吗 我能不能考虑开个大口
You know, could I consider the big trousers?
我可以提要求吗
Could I fill them out?
你知道 因为我从...你哥哥们那里听到
You know, 'cause I've been eating a lot of shit from the...
太多扯淡的东西了 你知道吗
from the kids' menu. You know?
-我真的听了太多狗屁了  -我知道 宝贝
- I really have. - I know, honey.
他快死了 全身都是癌症
He's dying. Riddled with cancer.
罗曼...
Rome...
怎么了 这个玩笑很有趣啊
What? It's a funny joke.
"老爸得了癌症" 这有什么不好笑的
"Dad's got cancer". What's not funny about that?
变态的小儿子
Sick puppy.
但是 嗯 他让我管理公司
No, but, um, he asked me to run the company.
我在开玩笑 我是在开玩笑吗
I'm kidding. Am I?
小西
Shiv!
-那...演播室 首席财务官  -嗯嗯
- So... The studio? CFO? - Mm-hmm.
挤掉卡尔
Kill Karl.
小西 牙医准备好了
Shiv, dentist is ready.
怎么样
So?
怎么样 你现在是他最好的伙伴了吗
So, what are you, best pals with him now?
你已经达成交易了吗
Have you done a deal?
好了 小西 跟我说说
Come on, Shiv. Talk to me.
卖吗
Sell?
好吧
All right.
好吧 从我的角度来看 说实话 好的
Fine, from my perspective, truth be told, yeah.
卖掉会很棒 这样我的职业生涯不会再有任何倒退了
Selling would be great. No more blowback with my career.
我会拿走我的那份钱 五年来
I'll take my money. Five years' time,
我都很想摆脱这家公司和罗伊的名号
I'd like to be free of this company and the Roy name.
这家公司对我来说意义重大
This company means a lot to me.
是的 当然 爸爸 那就这样好了 你留着 就当是一家玩具店
Yeah, sure, Dad. So, fine. Keep it. It's a toy shop.
出于感情原因继续运行
Keep running it for sentimental reasons
直到你入土
until you nod out.
-就这样吗  -嗯
- That's it? - Mm-hmm.
公司没前途了吗
No hope?
好吧 如果你真的很感兴趣...
Well, if you wanted to get into it...
听着 你必须忘记一切 把它做成IBM好了
Look, you'd have to forget everything, IBM it.
我没有认真考虑过这事 但显而易见的是
I haven't really thought, but what's obvious is,
关掉烧钱的企业
shutter the businesses that burn cash,
或者启用能做得更好的人
or someone else does better.
我们生产视频游戏机 嗯 为什么
We make video games consoles. Hm? Why?
我们制作他妈的独立电影 为什么
We make indie fucking movies! Why?
我们有哪家主题公园赚钱了吗
Do we get a theme park ride out of it?
没有吧 我们他妈的
No? We have an arm
发射的电信卫星爆炸 炸掉了一只手臂
that launches fucking telecom satellites that blow up.
没有 为了未来重组公司 也许与经销商合并
No. Restructure for the future. Maybe merge with a distributor,
扩大公园 扩大游轮 砍掉新闻 报纸和电视
expand parks, expand cruises, lose news. Paper and TV.
新闻很麻烦 在中国 俄罗斯 中东建十个新公园
News is trouble. Ten new parks in China, Russia, Middle East.
你不需要他妈的新闻反馈
You don't need the feedback from fucking news.
对
Right.
但是 你这算是没有认真考虑过吗
But you haven't really thought about it?
嗯 这些只是显而易见的举措
Well, those are just the obvious moves.
很明显 我一直希望你们其中一个儿女来接班
Well obviously, I always wanted one of you kids to take over.
那 你觉得怎么样
Well, what about it?
这个我们已经谈过了 汤姆接班怎么样
Yeah, we've done that. What about Tom?
你接班怎么样
So.
没兴趣吗
No?
如果我继续运营 如果我们打一仗...
If I keep going, if we fight...
我必须指定肯德尔
I have to name Kendall.
是啊 是的 我知道这是什么情况了 我明白了
Yeah. Yeah, I see what this is. I see it.
你知道吗 我他妈的算是明白了 你做了一点肮脏的交易
You know, I fucking see it. You've done a little dirty deal.
怎么 你继续留着肯德尔 好灭掉收购计划 然后他...
What, so, you keep Kendall on to kill the bid and then he...
你在你一年之后下台时接管公司吗
he takes over when you step down in a year?
真他妈是笔肮脏的幕后交易
What a squalid little fucking backroom deal.
-他勒索你了 不是吗  -哦 小西
- He blackmailed you, didn't he? - Oh, Shiv.
不 不 我...我...如果他接管
No. No! I... I... If he takes over,
我会出售我的股份 是的 我会加入桑迪和斯图威
I'll sell my shares. Yeah, I'll join Sandy and Stewy.
我会让吉尔去找你
I'll get Gil to go for you.
我...我...我的意思是 我会杀了他 我他妈的杀了他
I... I... I mean, I'll kill him. I'll fucking kill him!
小西 为什么这么生气
Shiv, why so angry?
我...我还没和肯德尔达成协议
I... I haven't done a deal with Kendall.
我想干啥干啥
I do what I want.
而且 我已经决定要做的事情
And what I've decided I'd like to do
是正式要求你进入公司
is to formally ask you to come in
担当下一任首席执行官
and be the next chief executive of this company.
我觉得我不是合适的人选
I don't think I'm the right person.
嗯 你知道 我很聪明 我认为你就是合适人选
Well, you know, I'm pretty smart and I think you are.
你是 小西
You are, Shiv.
你是唯一合适的人选
You're the one.
我们是真的在谈这事吗
Are we actually having this conversation?
是的 我们确实正在谈这事
Yes, we are actually having this conversation.
那卖公司呢 也是吗 那是...那是怎么回事 是真的吗
And selling? Yeah? That's... What is that? Is that real?
当然 如果你不参与到公司来 是的 只能卖掉
Of course. If you don't come in, yeah.
靠罗曼吗 不行的
I mean, Roman? No.
靠康纳吗 哈 那还是卖了算了 对吧
Connor? Ha! I might as well sell, right?
爸
Dad!
你知道的 我建立这一切
You know, I didn't build all this up
不是为了让他妈的摇滚明星一样的总裁
to have some fucking rockstar CEO
跳着华尔兹来接管
waltz in and take over.
爸 我不这么认为
Dad, I don't think so.
真的吗 因为如果你真的不愿意进公司
Really? Because if there's really no hope
我宁愿卖掉变现
of you coming in, I'd rather cash out.
听着 如果我们是以这样的对话方式交谈
Look, if this is the way we're having this conversation anyway,
那么 好吧 卖掉好了
then yeah, fine, sell.
好的 那我卖了
Fine, I'll do it.
马上
Right now.
我会发推文 市场会变动 然后就这样了
I'll tweet, the markets will move, and that'll be that.
瞎扯
Bullshit.
你不在乎我卖掉公司吗
You don't care if I sell?
爸爸 别这么混蛋
Don't be a fucking jerk, Dad.
你愿意加入吗
You wanna do it?
是的
Yes.
是的 当然 我会感兴趣 除非这是真的
Yes, of course, I'd be interested. If it's real.
这是真的
This is real.
是的 当然 爸爸 我能做到
Yes, of course. Dad, I can do it.
我可以...我会...
I could... I would...
你为什么从来不问我 为什么
Why did you never ask me, huh?
我会大获全胜 我他妈会干到毁天灭地
I would kill this. I'd fucking destroy it!
没错
Yes.
这真棒 西沃恩
This is wonderful, Siobhan.
这是真的吗
This is real?
这是真的
This is real.
记住这个 光明的倾向
Remember this, this slant of light.
记住这个
Remember this.
就是这个
This is it.
好吧 我们需要好好谈谈这事
Well, we're gonna need to talk about it.
目前 我们需要保守这个秘密
For now, we need to keep this between us.
我要想想汤姆 吉尔...
I gotta think about Tom, Gil...
当然 无论如何 我们必须考虑好人员的编排
Of course. We have to think about the choreography anyway.
我的意思是 让你了解最新情况 给你设置一条快速通道
I mean, get you up to speed, you know, fast track you.
等你有了经验...
And as soon as you have the experience...
我们就指定你接班
we name you.
好吗
Yes?
好
Yes!
我操
Fuck.
好 没问题
Yes. All right.
好
Yes.
哈
Ha!
怎么了
What?
啊 只是我的经销商
Ah, it's just my dealer.
伟哥经销商吗
Viagra?
古董经销商
Antiquities.
嗯 我的投标人在帮我竞拍一套物品
Um, there's a package of items my bidder is in for.
啊 天哪 有什么不可以呢
Ah, hell, why not.
-竞拍呢  -呃 拿破仑的
- Like what? - Uh, Napoleonica.
只是一些物品
Just some items.
包...包括拿破仑的鸡鸡
In... Including Napoleon's penis.
那不是主要物品
That's not the central item.
是...是一套东西
It's... just a package,
有一些信件和其他一些文物 但是 是的
with some letters and some other artifacts, but yes,
鸡鸡也在一起卖
that has come to market.
拿破仑的鸡鸡
Napoleon's penis?
对于严肃的学者来说 这显然不是
Mm. It's obviously not an item of interest
什么感兴趣的物品 但是作为古董 当然不错
to serious scholars, but as a curio, sure.
一位英国外科医生将他的鸡鸡剪掉了
A British surgeon snipped it off.
康纳打算收购拿破仑的鸡鸡
Connor's trying to buy Napoleon's dick.
嗯 这很正常 是腌在罐子里的还是...
Hmm. Naturally. Is it pickled in a jar, or... ?
是干的 是的 现在真的没什么可看的了
It's dried. Yeah, really not much to see now-a-days.
是的 它有点像 就像一条牛肉干
Yeah, it's kinda like, what, like a strip of beef jerky?
是的 从历史的角度讲 这只是一件小事
Yeah, it's a mere trifle, historically speaking.
那么 你打算干嘛 得到那个和希特勒的蛋蛋吗
So, what are you gonna do? Get that and Hitler's nutsack?
然后混合成一款"接管欧洲"的冰沙吗
Blend it into a take-over-Europe smoothie?
嘿 怎么样
Hey, how'd it go?
嗯 挺好 他把公司给我了
Yeah, cool. He offered me the company.
我告诉他 呃
I told him to, uh,
派你去洪都拉斯了解一下菠萝的生产情况
send you to look at pineapple production in Honduras.
嘿 所以 怎么样 他说什么
Hey. So? How'd it go? What did he say?
-呃 是的  -我要去管哪里
- Uh, yes. - Where am I going?
-我们的计划怎么样  -有很多选择
- How's the plan? - Lot of options.
天啦 小西
Jesus, Shiv!
你这是要给我什么他妈的好消息啊 有多好啊
What have you fucking landed me? Is it huge?
嗯 我有一些手段
Yeah. No, I had some leverage.
-是吗  -而且 呃...
- Yeah? - And, uh...
我让你进了集团的核心层
I got you into the belly of the beast.
全球广播新闻的要职  泛美网络科技 宝贝
Chair of Global Broadcast News. ATN, baby.
我操
Shit.
天哪 哦 我的天啦
Holy shit! Oh, my God!
等等 有没有...那个怎么...那个 呃...
Wait, is there a... What about... What's, uh...
是和悉德·皮奇搭档吗
Does it fit with Cyd, Peach?
职务会重叠吗
Is that an overlap?
-是的 爸爸喜欢这样  -好的
- Yeah, no. Dad likes that. - Okay.
你知道的 两个竞争者 一个位置 他最喜欢看别人竞争了
You know, two contenders, one chair, that's his favorite.
-这是邀请你担当重任  -哇
- It's an invitation to step up. - Whoa.
你得吃掉桃子[皮奇] 宝贝
You gotta eat the Peach, baby!
-我操 全球广播新闻  -嗯嗯
- Fuck! Global Broadcast News. - Mm-hmm.
-哇  -是的
- Wow. - Yeah.
那么 你...你说了些什么
So, what did you... What did you say?
他不卖...他不卖了吗
Is he not s... He's not selling?
他有没有给你更多股份
Did he offer you more stock?
没有 他 呃...玩了一堆心理游戏
No, he, uh... Bunch of mind games.
好的
Okay.
嗯 你知道 典型的老爸
Um, you know, classic Dad.
好的
Okay.
-下午好  -下午好
- Afternoon. - Afternoon.
怎么回事
So?
怎么了
What is it?
我看见你了
I see you.
先生
Sir?
我们在电话里说过 不是吗
We spoke on the telephone, isn't that right?
是的
Yes.
你有点欺骗我 好意思说自己干活很牢靠
You were chiseling me a little, on the stable works.
当我是个有钱的老傻逼吗
Rich old fucking guy!
我们会扣除30%的费用 当做我们的精神损失
We'll pad it 30 percent, cream for the fucking cat.
不 先生 这项工作主要是时间和材料成本
No, sir, it was a time and material job straight up.
所以 当我设定20万预算上限的时候 你有点失望
So you got a bit disappointed when I set a 200K ceiling
所以你塞了一袋他妈的活浣熊
so you stuffed a fucking bag of live raccoons
-放在我的烟囱里腐烂  -没有 先生
- to rot in my chimney? - No, sir.
"没有 先生 没有 先生 是装满了三袋 先生 "
"No, sir, no, sir, three bags full, sir."
滚开 看着我回答
Fuck off! Look at me.
不 先生 不知道你说的事
No, sir. Don't know about that.
是吗 好吧 我全部付给你10万块
Yeah? Well, I'll pay you 100 grand all in
这事就结了
and we're done.
那点钱...连材料成本都不够 先生
That... That that won't even cover the materials, sir.
我无法接受
I can't do that.
想把我臭走吗 我他妈不会接受的
Try to stink me out? I won't fucking have it!
先生 这个活得花费30万 价格是这样...
That was a 300-grand job, sir. That was the price...
是吗 好吧 起诉我吧 祝你好运
Yeah? Well, sue me. Good luck.
先生
Sir!
我的律师曾经为司法部工作
My lawyer used to work for the Justice Department.
你的律师是谁 他妈的脱线先生吗
Who's your lawyer? Mr. fucking Magoo?
噢 天啦
Oh, God.
伙计们 在我们分别之前
Folks, uh, before we break up.
我想说一句话
Can I say a word?
是的 长官 船长 收到
Yes, sir, captain, sir!
听着 听取了你们所有人 你们这些
Listen, after taking soundings from all of you,
我最亲近的最爱的人的意见后
my nearest and dearest,
看来我的朋友莱尔德有一个好点子
it seems my friend Laird had a good point.
在三到四年的时间内 我想...
In three- or four-years' time, I think...
只留下一个传统媒体运营部门
there will only be one legacy media operation left.
好吧 我想说...
Well, I say...
就这么定了
let that be us.
-喔 棒 - 他妈的 真棒
- Whoo! Yes! - Fuck yeah.
-一家公司...  -好吧
- One firm... - All right!
...来对抗科技的潮流
... to stand up to tech.
只留下一家公司 最后坚持下去
One firm left, last man standing.
我们将成为世界上最大的传媒集团
We're gonna be the number-one media conglomerate in the world.
那太好了 爸爸 那样很棒
That's great, Dad. That's great.
说得真好
Here, here.
哪里可以搞到人工水果饮料
Where can I get some of the Kool-Aid?
我想要一些
I want some of that.
肯德尔和罗曼将担任联合首席运营官
Kendall and Roman will act as co-chief operating officers
而我会亲自投入时间
while I personally devote my time
对抗这次收购计划
to the fight against this take-over.
对不起 你...你刚刚是说联合吗
Excuse me, did... did you just co-chief?
不...不 他又回公司了吗
N... No, he's coming back?
我们必须团结一致 比以往任何时候都要团结
We need to stick tight. Tighter than ever now.
但是他...不 对不起 不好意思...
But he... No, sorry. Excuse me. Um...
他...他企图帮你最大的劲敌接管你的公司
He... He tried to help your oldest enemy to take over
结果却得到了晋升 是这么回事吗
and he gets a promotion, is that what's happening?
这是我的决定
That's my decision.
好吧 这纯粹是瞎扯淡
Well, it's bullshit.
你会指定一个接班人吗
And are you gonna name a successor?
经过一番考虑
After some consideration,
我想我们现在只是需要给出一个名字
I think we just need a name to flag privately
让大投资者私下里知道就行 我的意思是 可以是任何人
to big investors for now. I mean, could be anyone.
反正我还在这呢
I'm not going anywhere.
我的意思是 就算是一件毛绒衬衫也无所谓
I mean, it could be a stuffed shirt.
格丽 有可能是格丽
Gerri. It could be Gerri.
现在 你们就当成是格丽
Now, you might just as well say Gerri.
-祝贺你  -哇
- Congratulations. - Wow.
哦 那好吧 谢谢
Well, okay. Thank you.
不会是格丽 但是格丽很棒
It won't be Gerri, but Gerri's fine.
非常感谢你
Thank you very much.
这样我们就清楚了
No, just so we're clear.
不...不 我...我觉得很清楚
N... No, I... I think we're clear.
与此同时 肯德尔和我将在稍后回来
In the meantime, Kendall and I will be back later.
-好的 是吗  -是的
- Okay. Yeah? - Yeah.
我们得把一些他妈的浣熊塞进一个男人的烟囱里
We need to stuff some fucking raccoons up some guy's chimney.
好了 儿子 我晚点进去
Okay, son. I'll hang back.
嗯 你就 告诉他们 我正在打电话
Ah, just, uh, tell 'em I'm in the middle of a call
我跟着就进去
and I'll be right in.
好的
Okay.
好的 当然 爸爸
Okay, sure, Dad.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 你好 肯德尔
Okay. Hello, Kendall.
呃 我爸爸在路上 他...他得打个电话
Uh, my dad's on his way. He... he had to make a call.
他得打个重要电话吗
He had to make an important call?
这就像1987年的力量动作[霹雳舞] 老兄
That's like a 1987 power move, dude.
真...令人兴奋 怎么 你现在是他的向导吗
That's... exciting. What, are you like his Sherpa now?
你是他皮带上的骷髅头吗
You're like the skull, like, tied to his belt?
因为我他妈的害怕了
'Cause I'm fuckin' scared.
是的 好吧
Yeah, well.
所以你就这种"是的 好吧"的腔调就来了吗
So you're gonna come in here with "Yeah, well", hmm?
带着你这张脸和所有的一切
With your whole face and everything.
而且我的电话你一个也不接
And you're saying no to all my calls?
不 肯 你得给我透露点东西
No, Ken, you're gonna have to give me something.
告诉我他妈的发生了什么
Tell me what the fuck happened.
是的 只是 嗯 我不确定我们的愿景最终是否一致
Yeah, just, um, I'm not sure our visions aligned in the end.
嗯 我也操你妈
Yeah. Fuck you too.
你这样根本没任何道理啊
That doesn't even mean anything.
他抓住了你什么把柄
How did he get at you?
我只是重新评估了
I just reassessed.
如果你还想玩的话 我这个老朋友支持你
There's a friend card here if you want to play it.
你知道的 对吗
You know that, right?
我现在就站在你面前
There's a human thing standing in front of you.
你可以跟我说说
You can talk to me.
整个世界都在我们手中
We had the whole world in our hands
你他妈的却转身离开了 伙计 为什么
and you fucking walked, man. Why?
是的 我...我...我见过你们的计划 呃...
Yeah, I... I... I saw your plan and, uh...
我爸的计划更好
my dad's plan is better.
嗯 操你妈的
Uh-huh, fuck you too,
你这个他妈的优柔寡断的傻逼
you pusillanimous piece of fucking fool's gold,
他妈的富二代...他妈的混蛋
fucking silver-spoon fucking... asshole.
是的 他妈的接电话啊
Yeah, take that fucking call.
喂 爸
Hey, Dad.
好的
Okay.
哦 好的 是的 是的 我明白了
Oh, okay. Yep. Yep, I got it.
呃 他来不了了
Uh, he's not gonna make it.
他还有另外一个紧迫的事情
He's got another pressing matter.
噢 他有另外一个更紧迫的事情
Oh, he's got a more pressing matter
比我们从他手中夺走他的帝国还要紧迫吗
than us taking his empire off his hands?
桑迪爵士 看看风把谁吹来了
Sir Sandy, look what the cat dragged in.
你好
Hello.
嗯 我估计 嗯 我爸想让我问问
Yup, so I guess, um, my Dad wanted me to ask
有没有可能通过这种方式处理
is there any way through this,
嗯 就是 资产互换
you know, uh, an asset-swap?
收购以外的方式 呃 另外一种安排
Something else, uh, an arrangement that leaves you
既让你们开心 他又可以继续掌控
happy and him in control?
如你所知
As you know,
我们的立场是我们真的想全部收购
our position is that we're really after the whole thing.
对 那么 呃 他想让我告诉你们
Right, then, uh, he wanted me to tell you
显然 我们的公开说法是
to say, yeah, obviously our public line will be
我们正在考虑你们的出价
that we are considering the offer
但是你们出价多少并不重要
but it doesn't matter what you offer;
他永远不会向董事会推荐这个收购计划
he'll never recommend this to the board.
你们会损失大量金钱 他也会损失大量金钱
You're gonna bleed cash. He's gonna bleed cash.
战争永远不会结束
It will never end.
也许你们能干掉他
And maybe you'll kill him,
但是如果你们没有干掉他 他就会干掉你们
but if you don't, he aims to kill you.
他会在你们击败他之前
He will go bankrupt or go to jail
破产或入狱
before he lets you beat him.
他会干掉你们的业务 如果这不起作用
He will kill you on the business and if that doesn't work,
他会派人来阴的
he will send people around.
他会派人杀死你们的宠物 强奸你们的老婆
He will send men to kill your pets and fuck your wives,
这事会永远无休无止 我要传达的就是这条信息
and it will never be over, so that's the message.
很好
Good.
那 我们继续收购计划 好吗
Well, let's move ahead with that process, shall we?
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠